health-tourism.com 2013-05-02

# Health-Tourism.com - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our website, [www.health-tourism.com](http://www.health-tourism.com/), which is owned and operated by Find Global Care Ltd. (“FGC”). FGC takes your privacy very seriously. Please read this notice to learn more about FGC's privacy policy. 

## Limitations on Privacy Policy 

For purposes of this policy, Personal Information is any information or data about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, email address, phone number, etc., which are not otherwise publicly available. You will be able to use much of the features of the website without need of divulging any Personal Information to FGC. There may be instances, however, when you may be required to provide Personal Information to enable the latter to provide you with the information, data, or services that you have requested. Thus, this policy covers how FGC treats your Personal Information collected or received by or through the website. 

This policy only applies to this website. It does not apply to practices of companies or entities that FGC does not own or control, such as the medical institutions and health centers listed in the website, advertisers, and the like. 

## Information Collection and Use 

FGC may collect Personal Information when you use the features, information, data, and services of the website. Personal Information may also be collected when you register with FGC's website, visit or view any of its pages, or websites or pages of the medical institutions and health centers listed in its website. 

If and when you register with the website or make requests to FGC, FGC may ask for certain Personal Information, such as, but not limited to, your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, personal interests, medical, or health concerns, etc. 

FGC's website may also automatically receive and record information and data from your computer and browser, which are not personally identifiable to you, including but not limited to your IP address, cookies, software and hardware attributes, and the page or website you are accessing. FGC may use this information to customize the content and advertisements that you see, fulfill your requests, improve its services, address your concerns, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients of FGC. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure 

FGC, as the owner and operator of the website, does not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies, except to provide the information, data, or services you have requested, or under the following circumstances: 

  * When FGC provides the information to its trusted partners who work on behalf of or with FGC under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help FGC communicate with you about offers, promos, discounts, etc. 
  * When FGC responds to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise its legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * When FGC believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the website's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * When the website is acquired by another entity or if FGC is merged with another company. In this event, however, FGC will notify you before information about you are transferred to another entity or company, by e-mailing you or by posting of a notice to this effect on the website. 

The website contains directory listings of medical tourism, health care and medical services available world-wide. The websites, thus, has many links to other independent websites run by medical institutions, health care centers, and advertisers that are separate and distinct from FGC. When you click a link found on the website, which directs you to another site not owned or under the control of FGC, you are deemed to be subject to the privacy and security policies of that site. 

When you send FGC an email or complete its online forms, FGC will not share your Personal Information with anyone outside of FGC, subject to the limits of this policy, with the exception of health care and medical providers who provide the service about which you have inquired. 

FGC takes proper care to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of your Personal Information, such as but not limited to, the installation of physical, electronic, and procedural methods of security. However, FGC cannot assure you that all Personal Information that it may collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. There may be instances of inadvertent disclosures, which are beyond the control of or not due to the fault or negligence of FGC. As a consequence, FGC disclaims any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or non-disclosure of your Personal Information. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy 

FGC may update this policy from time to time. FGC will notify you about significant changes in the way it treats your Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address you have specified or by placing a prominent notice on the website. 

## Concerns 

If you have any concerns about FGC's privacy policy for the website, please send your comments/questions to contact.us@health-tourism.com
